Heat. Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Built on dead and broken trees. Best
foot freedom factory scene. Amber waves
of gasoline days on every screen. Big
wrapped in tip ball hats. Scream
fake news in mags history white on the
wall. Empire and bound to fall. We're
living in a bit of denial and consion
stars and lies on every
proud in a state of delusion
while bridges collapse. We chase the
dream with broken maps. Healthcare
schools approve but we still laugh at
foreign polusion.
Truth is compass justice reason
allegiance to confusion. for being out
in a delusion.
This is financing
tick tock civil wars and home
is delusion
destiny massusion conspiracies on the
new constitution
for evolution
illusion with a punch
[Music]